

Ernesto Carrillo Guerrero

• Atlanta, Ga 2 404-528-9356 Hyundai Capital America Ernie0921 ©

Skills: (React | javascript | Node.js | Express.js | MongoDB | Postgres | SQL | SASS | HTML | jQuery | Bootstrap | Git | Github

Projects

Date-Night

This application recommends dinner and events based on location. Once all the information hs been enter you will be prompted with different options to select. An email can be sent to the client with the dinner and event selections at the end.

CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, HTML, API

Top-News-Api

Clients are able to stay up to date with the latest news happening around the world. This responsive web application allows the user to search and connect to articles.

HTML, CSS, Fetch, JavaScript

Moments

capture-moments.netlify.app/ github.com/Ernie0921/Moments

Allows Clients to save a postcard card with and image, brief description and location. The application was a way to allow users to share their travel experiences

HTML, Shell, JavaScript, MongoDB, Redux, React

Experience

Hyundai Capital America

Jul 2016 to Present

Funding Analyst Atlanta, Ga

In my current role I am responsible for reviewing, booking and funding retail and lease contracts from Hyundai, Kia and Genesis automobile dealerships. I communicate with dealership personnel, HCA sales and the Credit team. I must be strong with my attention to detail for I am required to review and verify all document information, and ensure conformance to HCA credit approvals, policies, and established guidelines. In addition,

perform all other duties as assigned including back-up for customer interviews, collateral verification inquiries and other investigative verifications as required.

T-mobile Jan 2015 to Aug 2016

Sales Associate Atlanta, Ga

The main focus of my role was to create a positive customer experience by providing excellent customer service and by performing consultative selling of T-Mobile products and services. I was responsible for keeping up with my Knowledge of the rapidly evolving T-Mobile standards and technology and guide customer through purchasing experience. In addition, I acted as technical support for existing customer facing issues with their devices. Once a customer was onboarded onto our network it was my duty to keep track of their account and assist in keeping the account updated.

Education

DigitalCrafts: Full-stack development bootcamp

Nov 2020 to Jun 2021

Certification of Completion, Web Development / Programming

Kennesaw State University

Aug 2015

Accounting, Finance

Languages

Spanish Fluent